Guide to the New York University Archives Audiovisual Collection AV
New York University Archives
- Audiovisual Recordings
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000 edited master reel 4, circa 1967; AV306; 1 sound tape reels (Box Digitized Access Files, E-records AV306)
    Original tape box includes following note: "By the Year 2000 edited master reel 4"
    - Original Recording (Box 9, Reel 306)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:34)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000 edited master reel 5, circa 1967; AV307; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes following note: "By the Year 2000 edited master reel 5"
    - Original Recording (Box 124, Reel 307)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:35)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV308; 1 sound tape reels (Box Digitized Access Files, E-records AV308)
    Original tape box includes following note: "'Year 2000' series two, reel #1, original master"
    - Original Recording (Box 7, Reel 308)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:29)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV309; 1 sound tape reels
    Other Finding Aids
    Original tape box includes following note: "'Year 2000', Series two, reel #2, original master"
    - Original Recording (Box 8, Reel 309)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:42)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV310; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes following note: "Yr 2000 Master Part I Series 3"
    - Original Recording (Box 8, Reel 310)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:39)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV311; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes note: "Yr 2000 Master Part III, Series 3"
    - Original Recording (Box 8, Reel 311)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:45)
  - In the Year 2000: By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV321; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes following notes: "By the Year 2000 cuts 4:10 each," "Reel 5: Cust, Kantrowitz [?], etc. Hunt, Q[?], Yang"
    - Original Recording (Box 8, Reel 321)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:43)
  - In the Year 2000: Glimpses of Life in the Year 2000 (audition), circa 1967; AV322; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box labeled with following notes: "Audition," "(5 min shows)"
    - Original Recording (Box 8, Reel 322)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:44)
  - In the Year 2000: Bennett Cerf, Dr. E. Cuyler Hammond, Mr. Kenneth, Dr. Franklin Dixon, John Tebbel -- By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV355; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes following note: "By the Year 2000 Reel #1: [struck through] Bennett Cerf 4.10; [struck through] Dr. E. Cuyler Hammond 4.12; Mr. Kenneth 4.10; [struck through] Dr. Franklin Dixon 4.10; [struck through] John Tebbel 4.09"
    - Original Recording (Box 9, Reel 355)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:30)
  - In the Year 2000: Hubert H. Humphrey, Dr. Rev. Donald Harrington, Dr. Bentley Glass, Ulrich Franzen, Dr. Louis Gerstman -- By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV356; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 9, Reel 356)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:31)
  - In the Year 2000: Al Capp, Betsy Johnson, Walter Sullivan, Morton Subotnick -- By the Year 2000, circa 1968; AV357; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 9, Reel 357)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:24)
  - In the Year 2000: Al Capp, William Quirk, Betsy Johnson, Walter Sullivan, Morton Subotnick -- By the Year 2000, circa 1967; AV358; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box includes following note: "By the Year 2000 Reel #3: Al Capp 4.09 12/6/67; [struck through] William Quirk 4.02; Betsy Johnson 4.08 1/1/68; Walter Sullivan 4.10 1/16/68; Morton Subotnick 4.08 3/1/68"
    - Original Recording (Box 9, Reel 358)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:32)
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. Roger Revelle, Walter Sullivan, Dr. Ethel Alpenfels, Sylvester "Pat" Weaver, Dr. James Hester -- By the Year 2000, January 1968; AV359; 1 sound tape reels
    Original tape box labeled with following notes: "By the Year 2000 Reel #4, Dr. Roger Revelle 1/8/68, Walter Sullivan (part 2), Dr. Ethel Alpenfels 9/30/68, Sylvester "Pat" Weaver 1/9/68, Dr. James Hester 1/15/68"
    - Original Recording (Box 9, Reel 359)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:33)
  - In the Year 2000: Dr. Roger Revelle, Walter Sullivan (part 2), Dr. Ethel Alpenfels, Sylvester "Pat" Weaver, Dr. James Hester, circa 1967; AV360; 1 sound tape reels
    - Original Recording (Box 9, Reel 360)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 115, Cd 12:25)
  - Discussion with Mayor of Paris, Jacques Chirac, January 14, 1983; AV1196; 1 sound tape reels Approx 9 minutes
    - Original Recording (Box 30, Quarter inch audio reel 1)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:20)
  - Discussion with French Minister of Justice, R. Badinter, January 21, 1983; AV1197; 1 sound tape reels Approx 83 minutes
    - Original Recording (Box 30, Quarter inch audio reel 2)
    - Access Copies (Box Shared University Archives 114, Cd 11:21-11:22)
  - TSOA Dedication Ceremony, 1982 December 9; AV1501; 1 sound tape reels; 1/4 inch audio (Box 39, Reel 1501, Box Shared University Archives 116, Cd 7)
    3 ¾ IPS 1/4 inch audio Scotch
    Access copy available on CD - ACCESS 13:7
  - [untitled dental/medical lecture], AV1999b; 1 sound tape reels (Box CD ACCESS 3:7)
    While the content of this recording was found on a tape supposed to be recordings of Dr. Sidney Hook's 1963 Introduction to Ethics class from Sunrise Semester, this appears to be a lecture or demonstration for a dental or medical class.
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 3:7.
  - Dental or Medical Lecture, Around 1963; AV1999c; 1 sound tape reels
    This appears to be a lecture or demonstration for a dental or medical class. The label indicated it to be recordings of Dr. Sidney Hook's 1963 Introduction to Ethics class from Sunrise Semester.
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 3:8.
  - Jazzy Lounge Music, 1966; AV2010b; 1 sound tape reels 00:35:51 (Box 2, Reel AV2010b, Box CD ACCESS 4:1)
    While the content of this recording was found on a tape supposed to be recordings of Dr. Kai Nielsen's 1966 Philosphical Analysis class from Sunrise Semester, this recording comprises jazzy lounge music. Soft speaking voices can barely be heard below the music; Other recordings from this tape can be identified by their Unique Identifier which begin with AV2010.
  - Untitled - Jazz, big band Radio show, Unknown; AV2022b; 1 sound tape reels; 1/4" audio tape reel (Box 2)
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 4:16
    Appears to be a jazz/big band radio show from the 1960s or 1970s - possibly a WNYU show? Found on a 1/4" audio tape with a recording of a lecture from Dr. Floyd Zulli's Sunrise Semester class - "Have You Read...?" The subject of the lecture was Thomas Paine's Common Sense.
  - Untitled Anatomy lecture, AV2023c; 1 sound tape reels; 1/4" tape reel (Box 2)
    The first 7:30 of recording appear to be part of an anatomy class in which the lecturer discusses several bones and muscle groups and even has a drummer perform in order to demonstrate how parts of the body work. Original tape held this recording and two lectures by Floyd Zulli for his "Have You Read...?" class on Sunrise Semester. Recordings on this reel can be identified by Unique Identifiers beginning with 2023.
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 4:18.
    Anatomy.
  - Untitled: Television programming and ads, 1960; AV2028c; 1 sound tape reels 23:05 (Box 2)
    Audio of television shows, news, and ads aken from a reel presumed to contain recordings of Professor Richard C. Harrier's class "Shakespeare: Complete Works," televised in fall 1960 as part of the Sunrise Semester program.
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 4:26.
  - Untitled Lecture: Episode of Social Philosophers of the Western World (partial), AV2035a; 34 minutes
    Pulled from a tape supposed to be part of the recordings of the Sunrise Semester program, recording comprises an episode of Social Philosophers of the Western World presented by Meeta (sp?) and the City College of New York with Professor Henry M. Magid. Recording comprises only 34 minutes of the 60 minute lecture.
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 5:9.
    Magid, Henry Meyer, 1917-
  - "From Myth to Reason", AV2035b
    Pulled from a tape supposed to be part of the recordings of the Sunrise Semester program, recording comprises an episode of Social Philosophers of the Western World presented by Meeta (sp?) and the City College of New York with Professor Henry M. Magid.
  - Eubie Blake, Roland Hanna, Danny Mixon Performance: Tape 2, October 10, 1973; AV2095; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Cassette 2095, Box 53, Reel 2095)
    Copies available on audiocassette and DAT.
    This is audio tape 2 of 2 from this event. The first audio tape is missing. The original video materials cover the entire event.
    This Eubie Blake, Roland Hanna, Danny Mixon recording was from an event which was part of a concert series called Jazz: The American Invention.
    Jazz; Blake, Eubie, 1887-1983; Hanna, Roland; Mixon, Dannie
  - "Hobbes and His Theory of Natural Mind and Civil Society", 1960; AV2037; 1 sound tape reels (Box 2)
    Pulled from a tape supposed to be part of the recordings of the Sunrise Semester program, recording comprises an episode of Social Philosophers of the Western World presented by Meeta (sp?) and the City College of New York with Professor Henry M. Magid; show is followed by 7 minutes of what appears to be a lecture on primary education or a news report about a middle school science fair.
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 5:17
  - Jimmy Breslin: Tape 1, February 28, 1974; AV2896; 1 sound tape reels 1 sound cassette (DAT) 1 sound cassette (Box 75, Cassette 2896, Reel 2896)
    This is audio tape 1 of 2 from this event. The second audio tape is missing. The original video materials cover only the second part of this event.
    This Jimmy Breslin recording was from an event which was part of a lecture series called Great Speaker Series 1974.
    Breslin, Jimmy
  - Thad Jones, Mel Lewis: Tape 1, October 24, 1973; AV2904; 1 sound tape reels 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 75, Reel 2904, Cassette 2904)
    Copy available on DAT.
    This is audio tape 1 of 4 from this event. The original video materials cover the entire event.
    This Thad Jones, Mel Lewis recording was from an event which was part of a concert series called Jazz: The American Invention.
    Jazz; Jones, Thad; Lewis, Mel, 1929-1990
  - Thad Jones, Mel Lewis: Tape 2, October 24, 1973; AV2905; 1 sound tape reels 1 sound cassette (DAT) (Box 75, Reel 2905, Cassette 2905)
    Releated Materials
    This is audio tape 2 of 4 from this event. The original video materials cover the entire event.
    Jazz; Lewis, Mel, 1929-1990; Jones, Thad
  - Thad Jones, Mel Lewis: Tape 3, October 24, 1973; AV2906; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Reel 2906)
    This is audio tape 3 of 4 from this event. The original video materials cover the entire event.
  - Thad Jones, Mel Lewis: Tape 4, October 24, 1973; AV2907; 1 sound tape reels (Box 75, Reel 2907)
    This is audio tape 4 of 4 from this event. The original video materials cover the entire event.
  - NYU Press Awards, April 18, 2000; AV3070 (Box 85, Item 3070)
  - NYU Press Prizes for Fiction and Poetry, May 1, 1997; AV3083; 1 VHS Approx. 40 minutes
    The innaugural NYU Press Prize award ceremony for fiction and poetry. This award replaced the Bobst award, which had previously been awarded to emerging talented writers.
    - Original Recording (Box 85, Vhs 3083)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 113, Dvd 10:27)
  - Bayrd Still, Walking Tour of Washington Square campus, 1981; AV3096; 1 audiocassettes (Box 86, Item 3,096, Box Shared University Archives 116, Item 8)
    Access Copy
    Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 13:8
  - [Campus Life], 1936; AV3167; Schult, Frederick; 1 film reels (Box 87, Reel 3167)
    New York University. University Heights
  - Modern Maturity, AV3278; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3278)
  - CBS Sunday Morning News, undated; AV3279; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3279)
  - The Open Mind, undated; AV3280; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3280)
    Richard Heffner and Jan Waldman also appear in this tape.
  - Larry Tisch Buys 25% of CBS (CBS-TV), AV3281; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3281)
  - Today Show (NBC-TV), undated; AV3282; Brademas, John, 1927-2016 (Box 90, Item 3282)
  - "L. Jay Oliva College Athletics" on Morning Program, CBS TV (tape 1 of 3), 7 March 2001; AV3283; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014; 1 VHS (Box 90, Cassette 3283)
    Existence of copies
    This recording has been digitized. Please contact the University Archives for access.
    College sports.; New York University -- Sports
  - "L. Jay Oliva College Athletics" on Morning Program, CBS TV (tape 2 of 3), 7 March 2001; AV3284; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014; 1 VHS (Box 90, Cassette 3284)
  - "L. Jay Oliva College Athletics" on Morning Program, CBS TV (tape 3 of 3), 7 March 2001; AV3285; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014; 1 VHS (Box 90, Cassette 3285)
  - Small Time Crooks/Woody Allen Q&A, May 3, 2000; AV3299 (Box Shared University Archives 110, Dvd 7:50)
    In the spring of 2000, Woody Allen did a two week tour of colleges and universities around the United States with his film "Small Time Crooks" starting at NYU. This is a video of events surrounding the NYU pre-screening, including students receiving tickets, reacting to the film outside of the theater, and engaging in a Q&A session with Woody Allen. Audio drops out at times when B-Roll audience reaction shots have been inserted to footage of Mr. Allen answering questions. (Preceded by bars and tone)
    Tisch School of the Arts; Allen, Woody, 1935-
  - Reina Webster - TV AD for New Zealand Scholarship Campaign, Undated; AV3309 (Box Shared University Archives 110, Dvd 7:51)
    Promotional video for a film scholarship in New Zealand, featuring previous recipient and NYU Tisch graduate, Reina Webster.
    Film.; Webster, Reina; Tisch School of the Arts
  - TISCH SCHOOL OF THE ARTS RECRUITMENT VIDEO: Film Students on a Shoot, April 22, 1996; AV3311; 1 Betacam_SP 30 minutes (Box Shared University Archives 111, Dvd 8:50)
    Video seems to be B-Roll for a recruitment video of students working with equipment and shooting in Washington Square Park.
    This is one of three tapes that seem to be B-Roll from the same recruitment video project. The other tapes are ref1350 and ref 1351.
    Washington Square (New York, N.Y.); Tisch School of the Arts
  - TISCH SCHOOL OF THE ARTS RECRUITMENT VIDEO: Sam Pollard B-Roll: Avid Training, April 23, 1996; AV3312; 1 Betacam_SP 19 minutes (Box Shared University Archives 111, Dvd 8:51)
    Recording of film editor and producer Samuel D. Pollard instructing students on the use of Avid Video editing equipment.
    This is one of three tapes that seem to be B-Roll from the same recruitment video project. The other tapes are ref1349 and ref 1351.
    Digital video -- Editing; video editing; Tisch School of the Arts; Pollard, Sam
  - TISCH SCHOOL OF THE ARTS RECRUITMENT VIDEO: Bami Adedoyin B-Roll-Student, April 9, 1997; AV3313; 1 Betacam_SP (Box Shared University Archives 111, Dvd 8:52)
    This is one of three tapes that seem to be B-Roll from the same recruitment video project. The other tapes are ref1349 and ref 1350.
    B-Roll footage for Tisch recruitment video. Includes people walking into the Tisch Buildling and students working on a video editing station. While Professor Bami Adedoyin is not featured in the video, his name is on the label, suggesting that he was involved in its production.
    Digital video -- Editing; Videocassettes.; video editing; Adedoyin, Bami; Tisch School of the Arts
  - Episode of British entertainment TV show, "Filmspotting", January 15, 2001; AV3314; 1 VHS 9:56 (Box Shared University Archives 111, Dvd 8:53)
    Historical note
    Filmspotting was a film industry "magazine" TV program on FilmFour in the UK between 1999 and 2002. (Source:Television and British Cinema: Convergence and Divergence Since 1990 By Hannah Andrews, 2014)
    Episode of British film-centric television show "Filmspotting" featuring a short segment on NYU's Film school, including an nterview with Associate Dean Dr. Sheril Antonio. Segment begins about 15 minutes into the recording.
    Antonio, Sheril D., 1960-; Tisch School of the Arts; FilmFour (Firm)
  - NYU Tisch School of The Arts (Recruitment Video), 1997; AV3320; 1 VHS RT: 15:50 (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:1)
    Three reels of footage are also included in this collection that apear to have been shot as B-Roll for this video. Unieque identifiers: ref1349, ref1350, and ref1351.
    Produced in 1996-97 by the Department of Media Production in the Office of Public Affairs at NYU, this is a Tisch School of the Arts recruitment video.
    New York University. Office of Media Production; Guarino, Elisa; Tisch School of the Arts; Campbell, Mary Schmidt
  - Episode of MSG Metro Learning Center TV show "School's Out", September 15, 1998; AV3326
    Episode of a show geared toward teens interested in the arts and humanities. There are large blank spots on the tape probably intended to be filled by commercials. This episode features a segment with Patrick Riviera, Director of the High School Summer Drama Program at Tisch School of the Arts. Patrick participates in a group interview about various summer arts programs for high schoolers. The segment starts at 23:20 and ends at at 28:10.
    Humanities; Arts.; Acting; Education |x Humanities; Tisch School of the Arts; Riviera, Patrick
    - Original Recording, AV_ref1371; 1 VHS (Box 92)
      Duration: 88 minutes; Business card attached to case: Richard A. Pierce, NYU, Office of Public Affairs, "Please return when finished. Thanks." (handwritten on card)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:4)
  - Dave Talks to NYU Film Students, A segment on the Late Show with David Letterman, April 6, 1998; AV3329
    This is a brief segment David Letterman did on the Late Show in which he speaks with Tisch School students about acting in their films. It is intercut with short scenes in which Dave plays bit parts, usually getting a laugh.
    Late show with David Letterman; Tisch School of the Arts; Letterman, David
    - Original Recording, 1 VHS (Box 92)
      Duration: 5 minutes
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:4)
  - The William H. Cosby Future Filmmakers Workshop promotional video, circa 1995; AV3343
    This is a promotional video for the William H. Cosby Future Filmmakers Workshop; a high school summer program at Tisch School of the Arts. It features interviews with alumni of the program and clips from some of the films the students made. "Special Thanks" are given to Clive Davis, Peter Lund and Harvey Weinstein, and William H. Cosby in end credits.
    filmmaking; Cosby, Bill, 1937-; Tisch School of the Arts; Davis, Clive; Weinstein, Harvey, 1952-; Lund, Peter
    - Original Recording, 1 VHS (Box 92)
      Duration: 4 minutes
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:5)
  - Interview with Louis Scheeder on MSG Metro Learning Center TV show "School's Out", February 23, 1999; AV3344
    Interview segment from "School's Out" a TV show geared toward teens interested in arts and humanities. Director of NYU's Classical Studio, Louis Scheeder is interviewed, discussing Shakespeare and the film Shakespeare in Love.
    Shakespeare in love (Motion picture); Scheeder, Louis; Tisch School of the Arts; Shakespeare, William, 1564-1616
    - Original Recording, 1 VHS (Box 92)
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:6)
  - Episode of Japanese entertainment TV show, "Cinematic Report", September 5, 1998; AV3348
    Cinematic Report appears to be a Japanese television show focused on the film industry. In addition to reviewing films, this episode features reporting on the top five film undergrad programs in the United States. The segment on NYU's Tisch School begins at 05:22 and is only about twenty seconds long. The report uses footage from the NYU Tisch School of the Arts Recruitment Video made in 1997.
    Tisch School of the Arts
    - Original recording, 1 VHS (Box 92)
      Duration: 28 minutes
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:2)
  - "NYU On the Air" - Clip Reel of NYU-related segments on TV shows, 1998; AV3349
    This reel is related to the RG 7.3.4: Records of the Department of Media Production
    Entitled "NYU on the Air," this reel is composed mostly of clips from news shows featuring professors or administrators from NYU. Clips come from The Late Show with David Letterman, Inside the Law, Giraldo Rivera, Legal Cafe, CNN News, CNN Showbiz, Seinfeld, and Cosby. Some of the featured guests are Dean of Stern School of Business George Daly, then Dean of NYU Law School John Sexton, Financial Aid Director Keith Jepsen, Director of Africana Studies Manthia Diawara and President Jay Oliva The reel was produced by the Elisa Guarino in the Department of Media Production and the Office of Public Affairs.
    CNN Reports; Cosby show (Television program: 1984-1992); Late show with David Letterman; Seinfeld (Television program); Richards, Michael, 1949-; Letterman, David; Oliva, L. Jay (Lawrence Jay), 1933-2014; Diawara, Manthia, 1953-; Cosby, Bill, 1937-; Seinfeld, Jerry; Jepsen, Keith; Gallo, Philip; New York University. Office of Media Production; Guarino, Elisa; Daly, George G.; Sexton, John Edward, 1942-
    - Original Recording, 1 VHS (Box 92)
      Duration: 8 minutes
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:8)
  - "Columbia University and New York University Film Schools: Free Film Voices", 2000; AV3354
    Documentary about the pros and cons of going to film school. Should a film maker spend money on the tuition of film school or just make a feature length motion picture for the same cost? These questions are asked and answered by students, alumni, and professors from Tisch School of Arts and Columbia University's film program.
    filmmaking; Columbia University; Columbia University -- Faculty; New York University; Columbia University. School of the Arts; Roach, Janet; Ferguson, Bruce W.; Reilly, William; Tisch School of the Arts; Dattilo, Maury; Campbell, Mary Schmidt; Insdorf, Annette
    - Original Recording, 1 VHS (Box 92)
      Duration: 41 minutes
    - Access Copy (Box Shared University Archives 112, Dvd 9:7)
  - Dedication of the K.V. Weissman Clinical Science Building, NYU College of Dentistry, Part 1, 1961 January 21; AV3394; New York University. College of Dentistry (Box 93, Reel 3394)
    Technical Access
    1/4" open reel original; Speed 7 1/2; Scotch Magentic Tape (3M).
  - Dedication of the K.V. Weissman Clinical Science Building, NYU College of Dentistry, Part 2, 1961 January 21; AV3395; New York University. College of Dentistry (Box 93, Reel 3395)
  - NYU College of Dentistry: Centennial celebration, dedication of plaque, 1965 January 27; AV3397 (Box 93, Item 3397)
    This tape is related to materials in RG 25, Records of the New York University College of Dentistry.
  - "NYU Tonight" profile of L. Jay Oliva, 26 April 2001; AV3426; 1 VHS (Box 94, Cassette 3426)
  - "The Open Mind" with Dr. L. Jay Oliva, 2 October 1996; AV3444; 1 VHS (Box 124, Cassette 3444)
  - Voices of the Encounter (tapes 1 and 2), undated; AV3483 (Box 95, Item 3483)